TYLER A. HANKERSON

Atlanta GA, 30301 Cell: 404-621-5356

Email: tyler.hankerson@gmail.com

Web Developer

Front-end web developer with a background in customer service, manual labor and music production. My unique experiences enable me to examine problems from a wide variety of angles from a micro and macro perspective. I thrive in team-oriented environments, but also have the discipline to work alone and complete any task given. I have a passion for acquiring new skills and strive to use them to better myself as well as those around me.

Skills:

Programming Languages: JavaScript, SQL, CSS, HTML

Platforms and Frameworks: React, Node, Express, MongoDB, SASS, Postman

Honorable Mentions: GitHub, Mongoose, Heroku, Bootstrap, Netlify, Object-Oriented-design, Testing, Algorithms, Data

Structures, Debugging, Responsive Design

Professional Experience

Software Engineering Scholar | General Assembly | Atlanta, GA | November 2021 - March 2022

- <u>Pokedex Pinpointer</u> Developed a one page website using HTML, CSS, and Javascript that allows the user to type in a Pokemon name and search for their number in the Pokedex. The data was sourced and utilized from a Pokemon API.
- Wavey Workouts Built a full CRUD workout routine planner which allows the user to sign up and log in using
 authentication and authorization. Once logged in the user can add and create a personal workout routine setting the
 name, equipment, reps, and sets.

Traveling Steel Specialist | Retail Repair | Dallas, TX | August 2021 - November 2021

- Construct, install, and repair steel structures for Home Depot stores
- Plans and implements the overall approach to meet the contracting objectives
- Fabricate, anchor and replace steel beams, frames, and cantilevers

Fitness Center Associate | Atlanta Athletic Club | Johns Creek, GA | November 2021 - March 2022

- Coordinated and managed various events and functions hosting 40+ members and staff.
- Cleaned and maintained the locker room and fitness areas using commercial equipment and chemicals.
- Prepped and served smoothies and other snacks to members.

Education

Studied Audio Production | Middle Tennessee State University | Murfreesboro, TN

Software Engineering Immersive Graduate | General Assembly | Atlanta, GA